<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string name="release_notes_description_140">
        • New Statistics section in your profile\nNow you can see the progress you\'ve made and a lot of joyful information!\n\n
        • Bulgarian and Ukrainian languages are added\nWelcome to the club, buddy!\n\n
        • Major UI improvements\nAnimations, better design, fonts, fixed visual bugs. All included!
    </string>

    <string name="release_notes_description_143">
        • Less ads\nAds appear less in short tests (15 secs, 30 secs).\n\n
        • More statistics\nStatistics became more informative.\n\n
        • Other improvements\nNow it\'s shown in a typed word list if an inputted word is shorter than the original.\n\n
        • Bug fixes\nFixed app crash on Android 12 and higher.\nFixed a bug that caused text suggestions not to work.\nFixed a bug when statistics displayed the wrong time a user has spent on tests.
    </string>

    <string name="release_notes_description_147">
        • Less ads \nAds appear less in 1-minute tests.\n\n
        • Other improvements\nSome \"under the hood\" changes to improve app stability.
    </string>

    <string name="release_notes_description_148">
        This is more of an \"under the hood\" update. It will make future updates much easier.\n
        • Less ads\nAds appear less in most games.\n\n
        • Bug fixes\nFixed a bug when the last completed achievement in statistics could be displayed in wrong language.\n\n
        • Other improvements\nLanguages are now sorted in alphabetical order.\n\n
        • What to expect next?\nMore achievements, new game mode and some other features. Stay tuned!
    </string>

    <string name="release_notes_description_149">
        The main page has been redesigned!\n
        • Bug fixes\nFixed a major bug that, while playing, could cause the app to crash unexpectedly.\nFixed a bug when some statistics cards could be invisible.\n\n
        • Other improvements\nAdded the "Replay" button on the main page.\nThe results page now shows the difference between the current and the previous result.
    </string>

    <string name="release_notes_description_150">
        This update aims at the app’s optimization, bug fixes and some adjustments\n\n
        • 10-minute test! Now there is no reason to rush\n
        • All transitions between screens have been changed, they have become quicker and more responsive\n
        • The result screen loads much faster and the typed words list is moved to another window\n
        • The profile tab is slightly redesigned\n
        • The favorite Time mode statistics are back!\n
        • Fixed a bug when if a user had 0% progression, then the respective statistics card was locked\n
        • Fixed Ukrainian words with wrong characters\n
        • Now the game doesn\'t crash if a user reaches the end of a text
    </string>

    <string name="release_notes_description_current_version">
        • Now you can see both WPM (Words Per Minute) and CPM (Characters Per Minute) in the results!\n
        • Added Czech language\n
        • The English dictionary has become more universal. Words like color/colour, defense/defence are removed\n
        • Fixed the 0 WPM bug, when the WPM could only be calculated in a 60-second game\n
        • When a user is being switched to the result screen, the bottom buttons are blocked for a short period of time to prevent accidental clicks\n
        • Now it\'s less likely to crash when resuming the app after a while.
    </string>

</resources>